Everything that made one a stranger made you suspect.
One of the largest alien groups that lived in Europe was then the Jews.
The Jews end up in the scapegoat again.
Then it was like that ...
False claims
-That intentionally spread this infection.
They started to persecute and torture the Jews.
If we jump to the 1980s, it was a disease that spread in the world.
The virus was HIV and the disease was AIDS.
Many homosexuals were affected.
Some male homosexuals' lifestyle has initiated a rare cancer epidemic.
Homosexuality had just stopped being classified as mental illness.
Many lived in an idea that LGBTQ people were sick-
-And click on the worksheet.
In history, there is a tendency for us to baptize diseases for places.
-In completely incorrect.
-Right.
Type like Spanish sickness.
It was the brutal flu epidemic during the First World War.
And this ... Spain was a neutral country during the war.
They did not have war censorship in the news.
When disease cases began to dive up-
-reported Spain about it.
So it was unfairly baptized to Spanish illness.
East Asians have been exposed to threats during the pandemic.
Are there similar incidents with Italians?
Good question.
We have tried to check it.
It doesn't seem to be much like that.
When the cure of infection moved from Asia to Europe and USA-